<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Feed Monty</string>
    <string name="start_text">Press the button to feed hungry Monty!</string>
    <string name="start_text_emphasized">That\'s Monty, not the button!</string>
    <string name="ingredients_activity_title">Select three ingredients!</string>
    <string name="mixing_activity_title">Tap on the flask to stop mixing!</string>
    <string name="score_text">Your Score:\n%1$d</string>
    <string name="highscore_text">Your Highscore:\n%1$d</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy - Legal Notice </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_acceptance_text">I HAVE READ AND AGREE TO THE PRIVACY POLICY</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text"><b>Privacy policy for Feed Monty - 13.10.2021</b>\nThis privacy policy explains to you - the user - the type, scope and purpose of processing of personal data within Feed Monty.\n\n<b>Access rights</b>\nFeed Monty does NOT require the user to grant any access rights (which can be granted/revoked at any time in the system settings).\n\n<b>Data acquisition and storage</b>\nThe following user-related data is stored either locally (i.e. on the user\'s mobile device) or on Baldware servers:\n\n<b><i>1) Local storage of a high score</i></b>\nAfter each round (after each creation of a drink for the ingame character Monty) the user receives a score which quantifies the quality of the mixed drink. The highest and therefore best score is saved locally for the user as a so-called high score. This high score is not stored on Baldware servers. It is stored permanently (until the app is uninstalled or until a new highscore is reached) on the user\'s mobile device and only processed within the app. It is not available to baldware or other users of the app and is not passed on to third parties.\n\n<b><i>2) Local storage of information regarding the privacy policy</i></b>\nThis privacy policy is displayed to the user when the application is started for the first time. Whether the user agrees to it is stored locally so that the user doesn\'t have to read the policy on every start up. This information is not stored on Baldware servers. It is stored permanently (until the app is uninstalled) on the user\'s mobile device and only processed within the app. It is not available to Baldware or other users of the app and is not passed on to third parties.\n\n<b><i>3) Other</i></b>\nFurther personal data such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address are not recorded as long as this information is not provided voluntarily, for example when contacting Baldware via e-mail.\n\n<b>Use of third party services</b>\nFeed Monty may use the Google AdMob service to display advertisements. Ads are personalized based on the device the user is using. The user can deactivate this via the settings of his device.\n\nThe Google Admob service is provided by Google (Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA). Google is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement and thus guarantees that it will comply with European data protection law.\nGeneral information on user data acquistion can be found in Google\'s privacy policy.\n\n<b>User rights</b>\nLocally stored data CANNOT be deleted upon user request. Only the user himself can delete locally stored data by uninstalling the application on his smartphone.\n\n<b>Right of withdrawal</b>\nThe user has the right to revoke consent given in accordance with Article 7 (3) GDPR with effect for the future.\n\n<b>Right to object</b>\nFeed Monty can only be used without restriction by consenting to the privacy policy. However, personal data is only stored in certain cases (see: Data acquisition and storage).\nThe user can object to the future processing of his data in accordance with Art. 21 GDPR at any time. The objection can in particular be made to the processing for direct marketing purposes.\n\n<b>Change of the privacy policy</b>\nIn the course of the further development of Feed Monty, changes to this privacy policy may become necessary. Baldware informs the user in such cases, but nevertheless recommends reading them regularly.\n\n<b>Rights to the graphical content within Feed Monty</b>\nFeed Monty is a product by Baldware. All of the textures (including icons, pictures, animations, etc.) belong to Baldware and therefore to Andreas Baldinger. This does not include icons, styles, layouts, fonts, and other design elements provided by Google through the IDE Android Studio or external sources (e.g. fonts by Google Fonts).\nThe original creator of the animations is Miriam Kargerer who produced them on behalf of Baldware. Miriam Kargerer retains the rights to use them for any non-commercial purposes.\n<b>\nContact details of the provider/operator of the app (Impressum - Legal Notice)</b>\nAndreas Baldinger - Baldware\nHauptstraße 81c\n4232 Hagenberg\nÖsterreich\n+4367762065386\nbaldinger.software@gmail.com\n\nThis privacy policy can be viewed again at any point of time by tapping on the information icon in the top left corner of the start page of the application.</string>
    <string name="hint_title">Info</string>
    <string name="ingredients_hint_text">Select 3 ingredients for Monty!</string>
    <string name="mixing_hint_text">Tap the bottle when you feel like the mix is perfect!</string>
    <string name="hint_positive">GOT IT</string>
    <string name="ad_button_negative">MAYBE LATER</string>
</resources>